SAIKRISHNA GOUD THAMATAM

GIS ENGINEER

+91 7075553199



saikrishna.thamatam9@gmail.com



Hyderabad, Telangana India - 500098



SUMMARY

Bachelor of Technology(B.TECH) graduate in Civil Engineering, possess 1 year of valuable experience as a GIS Engineer. Serving as social service activist with an active involvement in Sri Sathya Sai Seva Organization, showcasing dedication to community and humanitarian causes. Strong problem-solving and teamwork abilities, combined with a solid academic foundation in Civil Engineering, makes me a well-rounded candidate in both engineering and social service sectors.

EDUCATION

Samskruti College Of Engineering and Technology

Bachelor of Technology in Civil Engineering (2019 – 2022)

Samskruti College Of Engineering and Technology

Diploma in Civil Engineering - (2016 - 2019)

Sri Aurobindo High School

Secondary School Education - (2016)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

 Software Skills: Familiar with engineering software such as AutoCAD, ArcGIS, LiDAR, Micro Station & MS Office

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

• B.Tech

Project Title: "Accessing the Durability and Strength of Flexible Pavement"

Description: A Case study on Accessing the Durability and Strength of Flexible Pavement. (12/2021 - 07/2022)

SOFT SKILLS

- Ability to work independently and as part of a
 team
- Able to handle multiple tasks simultaneously.
- Experience in managing Budgeting and Financial Handlings.
- Strong communication skills, both written and verbal, facilitating productive collaboration with team members, clients, and stakeholders.
- Adaptability: Quick to adapt to changing project requirements and technologies, ensuring flexibility in a dynamic work environment.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

GIS ENGINEER

DALE Technologies Pvt Ltd.-India | 2022 - Present

- Spatial Data Analysis: Analyzing geographical information to identify patterns, trends and etc.., which can be used for the entire land using all the in detailed features of point making.
- Urban Planning: Assisting in urban and regional planning by providing spatial data for infrastructure development, zoning, and land use analysis by feature point marking.

INTERNSHIP

- DALE Technologies Pvt Ltd.-India | 2022 August
- Visions India Pvt Ltd. | July 2021 -September 2021

Description: Constructions and Estimations of Constructions like Roads, Buildings& Retaining walls

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Team Leadership: Supervised a team of junior engineers, providing guidance to ensure project objectives were met ahead of a given schedule.
- GIS Project Success: Led a team in the successful completion of a complex GIS project on time and received recognition from senior management.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Experienced in utilizing GIS software (e.g., ArcGIS) to analyze geospatial data, create maps and develop solutions for complex spatial problems.
- Problem-Solving: Adapted to identifying issues, analyzing root causes, quality checking and developing solutions to overcome challenges.

SOCIAL-SERVICE PROGRAMS

- Youth Coordinator in Sri Satya Sai Seva Organization.
- Runner-up in Sri Satya Sai Youth Unity Cup tournament.
- Certification of Appreciation for Voluntary Blood Donor.